1.1.1 Updates to documentation
1.1.0 Added cadence feature plus commands to set and save settings
1.0.6 Change the GPIO sensor to be more multithreaded (one for each sensor) and faster to detect a rising edge
1.0.5 Changes to settings for Chronos Camera
1.0.4 Documentation updates and debug info in camera_control added 11-ftdi.rules for linux gpio
1.0.3 Bug Fix: added debug for end sensor
1.0.2 Bug Fix: added board_id setting
1.0.1 change to file format to accomodate windows pcs
1.0.0 Initial Version
